Apple
How could you be so cold, cold, cold?
Now you're bitter like apple, oh-oh
I thought you was my girl, girl, girl
Now you are just an apple, oh-oh
Nineteen, thought I found my wife
Shorty got a new job, workin' at the Five Guys
I don't eat no Five Guys, so I gotta find guys
that eat it, eat it, eat it
Shorty from Chicago
Thought she had the same heart as me
Boy, was I wrong
Thought she was a saint, but she a sinner
My good girl turned to a
How could you be so cold?
How could you be so heartless?
I thought you were my soul
Now I wish we never started
But it's my fault, I don't blame you, blame you
It was my loss, I can't blame you, blame you
It was my fault, I don't blame you, blame you
How could you be so cold, cold, cold?
Now you're bitter like apple, oh-oh
I thought you was my girl, girl, girl
Now you are just an apple, oh-oh
Now you're just a memory, not a friend to me
You turned enemy, got me in disbelief
It wasn't meant to be, now you're dead to me
You pretend to be who you're not
And I don't need you, no
She broke my heart
How could you be so cold?
Now I don't feel the same
Got some baddies in the line
But I don't know if I could trust again
Not to mention they don't really look like you
Don't look like you
I might have to spin again
On some of my old hoes
You know, bring it back to 2016
It's a cold world, I need to get my heart back
Bitch, you took it from me
Now I'm screaming, "Bring it back"
I know you didn't mean to
But now you got me singing, got me singing